你哪有专座啊
You don't have a spot.
-你今天是有什么毛病啊  -或许他因为
- What is wrong with you today? - Maybe he's cranky
未能按时间表如期如厕  心情不好
because he's off his bathroom schedule.
我能理解便秘的确会让一些人易怒
Well, I can understand how that would make someone irritable.
说一个有趣小知识  "易怒"这词来自拉丁语
Interesting fact: "Irritable" comes from the Latin,
"容易愤怒"
"Susceptible to anger."
我说出一个词
Just because I used a word
不代表我想听到他的语源学
doesn't mean I want its etymology.
有趣小知识  "语源学"这词
Interesting fact: "Etymology"
是来自希腊文的...
comes from the Greek word...
你好烦人啊  别闹了
You are being so annoying. Stop it.
你们两个是在笑什么笑啊
And why are you two laughing?
谢尔顿  他是在模仿你
Sheldon, he's being you.
他万圣节变装成你了
He's dressed as you for Halloween.